Marching to the New Wonderland
Her Highness Comes
Today, I helped an elderly ant cross the road
and earned another pennant.
I want a pennant, too.
I can give you one of mine.
No, that's yours.
I want to earn a pennant by myself.
How exactly do I earn a pennant, though?
Sparky,
just keep offering a helping hand,
and one day, a pennant will be yours.
Got it! I'll find people in need of help right now.
What
I’ll go check.
Where did they go?
Have you seen the bee princess?
No, I haven't.
If you see her, please notify us immediately.
We will reward you generously.
Does that mean I'd earn a pennant?
What are you doing?
Leave it to me.
I'll find Her Highness!
I will find the bee princess.
Where are you, bee princess?
Help!
It’s Her Highness!
Thank you.
You’re welcome, Your Highness.
The bee princess wouldn't be this dirty, would she?
Sorry. Wrong person.
Where are you going? Can I come with you?
Stop following me, little girl.
I have an important job to do.
With all of these dragnets,
the goats have no way to escape.
Yes!
Come here.
Come on, goat! Come into my train!
Have you seen the bee princess?
What "princess"?
I haven’t even seen a single bee.
Help!
I can explain!
I told you not to follow me, you know.
See? Hungry, aren't you?
Here, have some.
You already bit into that, though.
Hmph, fine.
Don't come crying to me later.
I haven’t bitten this part, yet.
Here you go. I haven't touched this cherry.
I only eat peeled cherries.
If I turn the cherry into juice,
she won't be able to see if it's peeled or not.
Here.
Have some.
The cotton on this bed is so uneven.
How am I supposed to sleep?
This is all we have. Take it or leave it!
Don’t go!
I want a bedtime story.
Once upon a time, there was a big hero.
He defeated the big, evil dragon
and rescued the princess.
Then, he earned the pennant of his dreams.
You're no hero.
You—
Leave me alone! Stop it!
Watch out!
You’re always running off and causing me trouble!
Just stop following me, alright?
I just wanted to make a cup of strawberry juice to thank you.
I hate you!
Stupid bees.
I’m getting revenge on you right this instant!
Hey!
Where am I?
An abandoned bee?
Let's go home, shall we?
Help me!
Let my friend go!
It's you!
Decided to come to me by yourself, huh?
You're going to regret that.
Come on out, Morning Sun!
Come on out, Sirius!
Go, Morning Sun!
Morning Sun?
I forgot that you can't attack!
Look out!
What a lovely day.
I've got mutton to eat and bees to vent at.
This is perfect!
Sparky?
I won't let you hurt her!
You...
She...
She’s not a bee. You’ve got it wrong.
Well, I'll check whether or not she's a bee.
Show your true self.
What’s happening? I'm blinded!
Aww, she's cute!
Why does she look kind of familiar, though?
I feel like I’ve seen her before.
Maybe...
She’s the bee princess?
Security!
Your Highness, are you okay?
It was he who kidnapped me!
Let me explain.
How dare you disrespect Her Highness!
There's nothing to "explain"!
Your Highness, spare me!
Little girl—
Princess Vivi,
take care.
Sparky,
I almost forgot to give you this.
I hope you’ll like it.
Open it, Sparky.
Maybe it's a pennant.
A lollipop?
Mmm! A thick honey flavor!
Look!
It’s my pennant!
END